How did you come up with the idea of promoting 3D virtual technology?
I have been developing virtual 3D technology for a long time.
It has been a long time since then.
Today, I would like to talk about how to promote 3D virtual technology
and how to promote 3D technology within the supply chain industry and within the brand.
First of all, from the MacKenzie's report in 2024,
we can see that the development of fashion and digital technology is a trend for the future.
All companies, whether it is a supply chain clothing company or a brand,
need to be on time in the process of digitalization development.
Keep updating the digital technology of the company,
keep adapting to the digital development,
so that in the field of clothing technology,
we can achieve certain breakthroughs or certain results.
Then the MacKenzie report summarizes the five trends for us.
First of all, the first is artificial intelligence and machine learning,
which is what we have been paying more attention to recently,
such as deep-seek,
and then there are 3D and virtual technology,
VR, AR, and finally blockchain technology.
Many people will also have such questions,
such as the accuracy of 3D design,
and we need to do it,
we need to do more practical things,
and will we use different software for different customers?
And can 3D design really replace physical samples?
And so on.
There are a lot of questions like this.
Today I want to discuss these questions with you in depth.
How should we do it within the company?
How to adapt to the 3D development trend?
And then make our own personnel structure more perfect.
First of all, let's take a look at the example of a Google Boss company.
As a fashion brand,
what we really need to do is surprise our customers.
Our ambition is to become the premium tech-driven fashion platform in the world,
and that 3D can help a lot.
We have really witnessed a huge transformation,
but really at Google Boss, we started really early with this.
The designers, the pattern makers,
everyone is working with 3D software.
To date, I would say almost at four to five hundred people
working with those 3D technologies here on the campus.
The transition from the classic design and classic way of doing things
to this 3D world has been really tremendous.
There's much more room to really think about what we want to do,
how can we be different this season.
There are heavy benefits of working 3D end-to-end.
We have reduced the amount of physical samples that we need to create a collection.
So teams are actually becoming so much more efficient
and, at the end of the day, creating better products.
Substance is coming in a very good place.
It's helping us to be better in digital and work faster.
We can really explore creation from scratch.
For me, working in Substance, it's super fun.
Even though I'm not a 3D artist,
I'm not coming from a 3D school,
I just learned everything here on the job.
The design idea gets visual and realistic from the beginning.
You have endless possibilities.
With a click of a button I see a color
that would usually take months or weeks to be shipped around the globe.
We have more time to be creative in the design departments
and, in the end, it's really good for the environment.
A key benefit that we're already seeing today
is the ability to use 3D also consumer-facing
and to create media and experiences
that haven't been possible
in classical kind of production processes before.
A really exciting initiative that we've been working on
called Imaginary Ones,
where we really collaboratively started to build digital products.
Really build and create that product that is super relevant
and that really speaks to that one consumer.
And with those new communities emerging,
we have the opportunity to do that.
And that's really what this whole transformation is about for us.
We're living right now a moment
which is like when the internet was created.
Every day is different.
Every day we have new opportunities and challenges
or whatever might come up.
But it's extremely exciting to witness
this transformation of the whole industry.
What is clear to us is that those virtual layers
will be omnipresent.
They will raise the way you experience a brand,
the way you experience a product,
the way you interact also with brands,
and it will be much more community-driven.
Okay, we just finished watching
Hugo Boss' presentation
on the use of 3D virtual technology
in the combination of one's own situation.
In fact, he extended from 3D virtual technology
to VR, AR, and digital space,
as well as the original universe, etc.
These prerequisites require us to have
a very accurate 3D clothing.
But for us,
as a supply chain company,
why do we use 3D to develop clothing design?
First of all, from our regular process,
we design, prepare the fabric, prepare the food,
and then review, and then finally pass.
But many designers, in some cases,
cannot make choices for their own designs.
For example, now I have a lot of styles,
or a lot of fabrics,
or a lot of patterns,
or a lot of patterns that cannot be decided,
which leads to the need for companies
to make many rounds of food samples,
which greatly increases the cost of sampling.
So after using 3D technology,
we can show these design solutions in 3D
in front of us one by one,
and then replace some of the food samples
with 3D clothes.
In the end, it is very convenient
to help designers make their own decisions.
In this case,
we can save a lot of clothes in the early stage.
And this is the real meaning of 3D design technology.
But some companies may be ahead of 3D design.
Some companies are relatively late in 3D design.
So let's take a look at these two 3D comparison pictures.
First of all,
the first one is a 3D work made
based on the understanding of 3D lace fabric
by some people.
The latter is the effect
made after we modified and optimized it.
So you can clearly see
that 3D virtual technology
actually requires in-depth understanding.
In fact, there is still a lot to understand.
For example, the material, texture,
and physical properties of the fabric,
as well as the entire pattern of the clothing,
as well as some operating settings
for its entire rendering, etc.
When we accurately use these,
use the correct platform,
use the appropriate pattern,
and then add the correct material
and physical properties of the fabric,
we can make
the real 3D design effect.
For example,
the first case,
this lace dress looks like
a thick carpet.
So it is completely
the opposite of what this dress
originally wanted to show.
So in this way,
it is difficult for customers to accept
your 3D,
whether it is the technical level,
or your understanding of this fabric.
So this will give customers
some bad impressions.
So the first impression
is very important.
So how can we promote our 3D?
And then in the brand,
and then let customers get more trust?
First of all,
I have prepared a checklist here.
everyone must follow
the correct 3D design process.
Or we have a professional term
in English called
VQS,
Virtual Quality Standard.
It is a name of a virtual standard.
Then we design a normal,
a standard,
a virtual 3D technology process.
In this way,
we can use the right version,
the right platform,
the right fabric.
The right fabric
includes materials
and physical properties.
When I meet all the conditions,
then we can do
what we want.
A real 3D designer.
The second point is
whether your 3D designer
has a foundation
like this.
If there is,
that is the best.
But if not,
then your 3D team
whether there is a
technical design
like this
a person
to support
a reasonable
test of your
version.
First of all,
if there are some problems with the version,
if the 3D designer
does not have a background like this,
it is very difficult to see
the existence of the 3D version
from the foundation of the 3D version
or the state of the 3D version.
So we need such a person
in our team
to check the rationality of the 3D version.
Because in the process of 3D,
there are many factors.
For example,
the physical properties of the fabric,
the rationality of the 3D version,
will lead to the final state of your clothes.
So we have to select them one by one
to investigate the reasons
that lead to the 3D design
and then to solve them.
So our team
must have a
TD who has a very strong
version technology
and we have an
excellent 3D designer.
Then they work together
to complete such a standard,
a complete 3D
trial process.
Another point is that
when our team
has more people
or the company
has more 3D
people,
we must have a manager
to control all of you
to send to the customer
such a rendering
or a public document.
Because the standard
that everyone makes,
the rendering pictures
are all different.
So we need a person
to control the quality of the 3D,
to ensure that
everything that is taken out of the company
is of high quality,
and that they are all premium
and then sent to the customer.
In this way,
we can gain the customer's trust,
so that the customer
can trust 3D more,
and be willing to interact with you
to help you save
the cost of your previous clothes.
There are also some questions
whether you have enough
good cases to convince the customer.
For example,
we and some customers
have already carried out
several trials
of such trial cases,
and then in the early stage
reduced the cost of
such a sample in several rounds.
With the assistance of these cases,
it will also increase
the customer's confidence
in 3D trial,
and then it will be convenient
for you to promote
the 3D trial technology.
It is also convenient
to reduce the cost of your sample
within the company,
increase efficiency,
and save time.
This picture is
an example of
a 3D trial we did.
On the left,
we tested the fabric
with the CLOUD
physical attribute tester,
and on the right,
we drew the effect of
the food sample
being worn on the platform.
You can take a look at this.
If you are satisfied
with all the requirements
mentioned above,
the correct platform,
the correct fabric,
and the correct version,
the 3D trial effect
you have made
is still very good.
Then,
you can also see
that in the upper right corner,
I also used
a software called Photoshop.
In fact,
in 3D software,
there are some functions
that need to be used
with the help of
some external software,
so that it can
achieve a more perfect effect.
For example,
Adobe Photoshop
and the two teachers
mentioned before,
Substance,
these software supports
help us to
achieve a more perfect effect.
This picture
is realized
with the CLOUD
hair dyeing technology.
You can see that
the hair dyeing effect
is still quite impressive.
Then,
this model
is a flat material.
The sleeves
are made of leather.
Then,
there are some
embroidery techniques
and straight hair techniques
on it.
I used the CLOUD software
and Substance Sampler
and Photoshop
to help complete
such a work.
So,
a good 3D effect
needs more software
to be used
with the combination
because different software
has different advantages.
So,
here
I also give
some suggestions
to companies
like us.
That is,
you can expand
your software library
and then
try to use
different software
to combine
to achieve
a more perfect effect.
Then,
this is a
bead embroidery
plus
the bottom
is a mesh
fabric like this.
Then,
the bead,
as you all know,
it has
a kind of
reflection effect.
Then,
it will reflect
different light
from different angles.
Then,
here,
I used
the bead made
by Substance Designer
and then
I adjusted the
parameters of
the bead
in the same way.
The advantage of using Substance
is that
it can
digitize
every part
and even
every thread
can be completely
changed.
So,
it can easily
change
the color
density
size
of each
component
and so on.
Then,
up to now,
our company
has worked
with many
partners
to
do
such a
3D
virtual technology
promotion.
Then,
we have
many
Adobe companies
and
some other
Amnon companies
and even
Blender.
Then,
another one
is
the brand
side
here.
According to
McKinsey's
fashion status
report in
2025,
there are
a lot of
problems.
Then,
these storage problems
will also
affect the
order
situation
like
our supply chain
companies.
For example,
when the brand
side
has too
much
storage
,
they will
reduce
the number
of orders
in the second year
and the number
of new
and new
products.
So,
we need
to
overcome
such a
crisis
or solve
such a
problem.
What can we do
from the perspective
of 3D?
In fact,
according to
the statistics
in 2023,
there are
5 million
remaining
storage
in the
world every
year,
and the
sales value
has reached
700,000
to 1,400,000
US dollars.
So,
the storage
problem
is a big
challenge.
The current
status of
customers is that
a large
amount of
storage
has caused
them to
take up
a large
amount
of
money
and
increase
the cost
of storage
.
The complexity
of management
will also
increase
and the
efficiency
of operation
will also
decrease
.
Therefore,
it is
very difficult
to
reduce the
order
.
What we
need to do
is to create
a healthy
life cycle.
Many companies
are trying
a model
of
small
orders
fast
return
.
It will
give you
a test order
first,
and then
carry out
a market
test
.
Then
,
if the
model
is
not
selling well,
it will
immediately
lower the price
and change
a batch of
new models
to continue
testing.
This is
a healthy
product
life cycle
management.
So
what can
3D technology
do in
this process?
It is
to speed up
the production
of
large
orders
in
front of
customers
.
In this way,
it can help us
quickly design
the model
that meets
the customer's
requirements
and quickly
generate
a small
batch of
test orders
and then
help customers
to test
on the market
.
After the
test
is over,
it will
quickly respond to the
demand of the market.
At the same time,
this is also a way to
help customers
to solve the storage
pressure problem.
I hope
that
this way
can make
customers willing
to accept 3D
and then
quickly
cooperate with
customers
to complete
such a
3D
test
and 3D
promotion
process.
Then
we
have to
talk about
the market
of AI
design.
So
AI and 3D
can also
be used
in combination
.
On the left
is an effect
picture of
our 3D
style.
Then
we can use
AI technology
to enhance
its
reality
and then
make this model
more real.
The wrinkles
on the clothes
will also
become more
real.
It will help
everyone
to achieve
a more
realistic effect
and then
help
everyone
in the
promotion
or in the
e-commerce
display.
It plays a
very
big
role.
There is another
one that is
more helpful
to everyone,
which is
the AI generation
style picture.
Because
the development
of AI technology
is still
relatively
advanced,
our designers
can
reduce
the time
of drawing
pictures.
These are
some of the
very
useful
help
that digital technology
and AI
artificial intelligence technology
have developed
to us
now.
So
I hope
everyone can
embrace
digitalization
and
embrace
AI
to adapt
digitalization
and AI
to a
better place.
Then
let's
promote
3D technology
and AI technology
together
and
use it
in our
actual
enterprise
to combine
the situation
of our
own
enterprise
in the
operation
or
design
process.
And
that's
all
I have
to say
today.
Thank you.